A Guide to the Records of Lieutenant Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 1995-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Legislation Files & Supporting Documentation, 1992-2005 (bulk 2002-2005)., Extent: 28 boxes. (Box 72-100)
  - Subseries B: Legislative Issues (2002 Session), 2000-2004., 2 boxes.
    - Education
      - Teacher Corps, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 35)
      - Teacher Evaluations in Georgia, undated (Box 74, Folder 36)
      - Teacher Home Loans, 2001 (Box 74, Folder 37)
      - "Teaching Kids About Investing", 2001 (Box 74, Folder 38)
      - Virginia 21, undated (Box 74, Folder 39)
      - Virginia Education Association, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 40)
      - "Way Out of School Budge Crisis", 2002 (Box 74, Folder 41)
      - Youth Leadership Initiative, undated (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Electric Generating Facilities (S.B. 554), 2002 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Emergency Contraception, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Game Department Funding, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Goodwill, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Greaser, Dr. Raymond D., 2001 (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Infectious Diseases, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - In God We Trust Bills, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - International Associates, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Kibbler, Jim, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - Medicaid (S.B. 658), undated (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - Motor Fuels Tax (S.B. 458), 2002 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Parental Consent, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - Partial Birth Abortion (H.B. 1154), undated (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Priority Bills, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Public Defender Commission, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - Sabato, Dr. Larry D., 2001 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Sales & Use Tax Bill
      - Senate Bill 16, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Senate Bill 170, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Sodomy, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Staggered Terms for Bath County School Board (S.B. 191), 2002 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - State Rehabilitation Tax Credits, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Terrorism, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Transportation, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Transportation Financing, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Bankers Association, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Dept. of Health, 2000-2001 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Virginia First Cities, 2001-2002 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Forests, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Health Care Foundation, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Virginia League of Conservation Voters, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Literacy Leadership Council, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Municipal League, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Performing Arts Foundation, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification & Community Revitalization Commission, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Subseries C: General Files, 1992-2005., 25 boxes.
    The General Files subseries is housed in twenty-five archival boxes and is arranged in alphabetical order. This subseries consists of supporting documentation maintained in the Lieutenant Governor's Office as background material for legislation and various social & political issues. Noteworthy are the files related to the budget, education, environment, healthcare, redistricting, and transportation. Also significant are files pertaining to Hurricane Isabel, public safety, standards of learning (SOLs), and waste management. The subseries contains correspondence, reports, memorandums, publications, presentations, legislation, minutes, agendas, news clippings, speeches, and other sundry items.
    - 2-1-1 Virginia Business Plan, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - 9-11 Speech, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Abortion/Contraception Issues, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Adoption, 1999-2005 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Adult Abuse, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Aging, 2002-2003 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Agriculture, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Airport Security, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Alliance Center for Collaboration Education Science & Software(ACCESS), 2002 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - American Bar Association, 2003 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - American Red Cross
      - Board of Directors' Handbook, 2002-2003 (Box 76, Folder 12)
      - Board of Directors' Meeting, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 13)
      - Interim Strategic Plan, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Amtrak, 2005 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Arts, undated (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Arts & Cultural Institutions, 2001 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Base Realignment & Closure (BRAC), 2004 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Birth-Related Injury, 2001-2002 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Bonds, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Bone Marrow Donor Program, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Budget
      - 2002 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Building a Better Virginia Foundation, 2002 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Business
      - 2002 (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Cabinet Meetings, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Ethics, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Files
      - 1992-2002 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Finance Reform, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Cancer, 2002-2003 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Cancer Policy, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Career & Technical Education, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Career & Workforce Development, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Chambers of Commerce, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Charitable Service Organizations, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Commission, 2004-2005 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Child Abuse Prevention, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Child Support Enforcement, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Children, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Children's Data
      - 2002 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - 2003 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Chincoteague, 1995-2002 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Civil Liberties, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Clergy Child Abuse
      - 2002 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Coal, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Conflict of Interests Act, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Constituent Recommendations, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Council of Virginia's Future, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Covenant Marriages, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Sports & Entertainment Commission, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Death Penalty, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Defense - Joint Warrior Interoperability Demonstration, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Democratic Party, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Dept. of Correctional Education, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Dept. of Juvenile Justice, 2001 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, 2002-2003 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Dept. of Social Services, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Deregulation, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Desert Eagle Newsletter, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Disability, 2001-2002 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Domestic Partnerships, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Domestic Violence, 2002-2005 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Domestic Violence/Unemployment, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Drugs, 2001-2004 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Economic Development, 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Education
      - Boad of Education, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - Funding
        - 1999-2001 (Box 81, Folder 6)
        - 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - General
        - 2002-2003 (Box 81, Folder 8)
        - 2003-2004 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Higher Education
        - 1998-2002 (Box 82, Folder 1)
        - 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 2)
        - 2004 (Box 82, Folder 3)
        - State Council for Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - K-12, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - Standards of Quality, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Teacher Salaries, 2002-2003 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Community College System (VCCS)
        - 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 1)
        - 2003 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Elderly Issues, 2000-2002 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Electric Cooperatives, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Electric Deregulation, 2003-2004 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Emergency Management
      - 2002 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Energy Education & Advocacy (videotape), 2003 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Energy Policy, 2003 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Environment
      - 2002 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Conservation 2001-2004 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Energy Policy, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Policy, 2001-2003 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Equity Virginia Speech, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County Chamber of Commerce, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Family Foundation, 2001 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Fatherhood, 2000-2003 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Federal Government
      - Brookings Institution Publications
        - 2002 (Box 84, Folder 10)
        - 2002-2003 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Federal Grants, 2002 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Federal Mandate Report, 2003 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Firefighters, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - First Freedom Awards, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Flood Assistance, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Forestry, 2000-2001 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Foundation 2002
      - 2002 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - 2002 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - 2002 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Fraternal Order of Police, undated (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2001-2002 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Gang Deterrence & Community Protection Act of 2005, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Gangs, 2005 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Gay/Lesbian Issues, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - General Assembly Report Card, 2003 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - General Assembly Television, 2001-2003 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - General Policy, 2001-2003 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Georgia-Pacific Big Island Operations, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Commission on Efficiency & Effectiveness, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Green Spring Colonial National Historic Park, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Ground Lease, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Guns, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Gun Safety, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Harassment, 2002 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Healthcare
      - 2000 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - 2001-2002 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - 2002 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      - 2003 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - 2003-2004 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - 2005 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - 2005 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - 2005 (Box 87, Folder 5)
      - "High Performance Guidelines" (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Hispanics, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Historic Tax Credits, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Historical Perspectives, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Homeless Services, 2005 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Homosexuality, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Memberships, 2001 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - House & Senate Bills, 2001-2002 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Housing, 2001-2003 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Hunters for the Hungry, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Hurricane Isabel, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Illustrative Funding Options, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Immigration, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Initiatives & Referendums, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Inmate Education, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Insurance, 2002-2003 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Interstate-81, 2004-2005 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Issues Fairfax, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation
      - 2003-2004 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      - Steering Committee 2002 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Judiciary
      - 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - 2002-2003 2002 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Kings Dominion, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Land Use, 2003-2004 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Land Use/Development, 2004 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Law, 2002-2003 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Law Enforcement, 2001-2002 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Legislative Drafts
      - GATV 2001-2002 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      - Standards of Quality 2001-2002 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Legislative Report of the Assemblies of Maryland, Virginia, & the District of Columbia, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Legislative Research, 2003 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Literacy
      - 2000-2002 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Breakthrough to Literacy, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - California Early Literacy Learning/Extended Literacy Learning, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      - Early Childhood Literacy Programs, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
      - Early Intervention in Reading, 2002 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      - Improving Early Reading & Literacy, 1999-2002 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      - Indiana's Early Literacy Intervention Grant Program, 2000 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Literary Collaborative, 2001-2002 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Smart Start Initiative, 2002 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      - Success By 6, 2001-2002 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      - Success For All, 2000-2001 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Local Government, 2002-2003 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Local Social Services Consolidation, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Longwood University, 2001-2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Mandated Benefits Report, 2003 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Marriage, 1999-2002 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Marriage/Family, 2001-2003 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Medical Disability Waiver Program, 2001-2002 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Mental Health, 1998-2002 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Mie Prefectural Assembly, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Military Advisory Council, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Military Base Commission, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Military Family Relief Fund, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Mine Safety, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Minimum Wage, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Letters, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Motor Vehicle Legislation, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Municipal Policy, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Museums, 2000-2002 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - National Capital Minority Business Opportunity Committee (NCMBOC), 2003 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - National Conference of Lieutenant Governors, 1996 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Natural Gas Exploration, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - New Americans, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Northern Virginia Technology Council, 2001-2002 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Northern Virginia Traffic, 2000 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Office of Commonwealth Preparedness, 2005 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Office of the Inspector General of Mental Health, Mental Retardation, & Substance Abuse Services, 2004 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Office Policy Work, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Out-of-State Trash, 2003-2004 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Page County Landfill, 2003 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Performing Arts Foundation, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Personal Assistance Services (PAS), 2002 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Pesticides, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Policy Ideas, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Policy Memos, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Port Issues, undated (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Private Providers, 2002-2003 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Procurement Disparity Study of the Commonwealth of Virginia
      - Executive Summary, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - Part 1-5, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 12)
      - Part 6-Appendix, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Project Exile, undated (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Public-Private Transportation Act, 2004 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Public Safety
      - 2002 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - 2003 2004 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Put Virginia First, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - "Quality of Life in Virginia: 2004", 2004 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Redistricting
      - 2002 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - 2002 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - 2002 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Regional Drug-Free Alliance, 2002 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Report Card for America's Infrastructure, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Comptroller, 2003 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Report on Statewide Financial Management & Compliance, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Review of Information Technology Systems Development, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - School Budgets, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - School Sales Tax Holiday, 2001-2005 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Secretary of Administration, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Senate Finance Committee, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Sexual Abuse, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Sexual Harassment Policy, 2002 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Small Business Initiative
      - 2003 (Part 1) (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - 2003 (Part 2) (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Smarter Growth, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Smithfield Foods, 2003 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Smoke-Free Buildings, 2004 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Social Security, 2005 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Sorensen Institute for Political Leadership, 2002-2004 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Southwest Virginia Agricultural Association, Inc., 2002 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2000-2002 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Speeches, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Standards of Learning (SOL) Testing
      - Sections 1-6, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Section 7, 1999-2001 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Standards of Quality, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - State Bond Referendum, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - State Strategic Plan, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2004 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Financial Management & Compliance, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Streamlined Sales & Use Tax Agreement (SSUTA), 2005 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Taxation, 2000-2003 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Tax Policy, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Tax Referendum, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Tax Reform, 2002-2003 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Tax Restructuring, 2002 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Taxes, 2005 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Technology, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Tennessee v. Lane, 2003 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Terrorism
      - 2002 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - 2002 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Tim Kaine Leadership Group, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Tobacco, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Transportation
      - 2001-2002 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - 2002 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - 2003 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - 2003-2005 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Transportation & Planning, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - United Negro College Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Unity Day, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - University of Virginia
      - Budget Briefing, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 3)
      - Meeting, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
      - President's Report to the Board of Visitors, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      - Staff Union, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Urban Policy, 2001-2002 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Urban Renewal, undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Utility Deregulation, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Vaccines & Autism, 2004-2005 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Victims' Rights, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Virginia 2020, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Association of Counties, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Baseball, 2002-2003 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Chamber of Commerce, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Criminal Sentencing Commission, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - VDOT, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Farm Bureau, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Financial Perspective, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Foundation for Architecture, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Virginia FREE, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Virginia Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Information Technologies Agency (VITA), 2004-2005 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Israel Advisory Board, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Virginia Legislative Record, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Virginia Military Advisory Board, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Military Institute, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Port Authority, 2002-2003 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Poverty Law, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Quality of Life, 2002-2003 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Retirement System, 2002-2004 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Sexuality Laws, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Sheriffs' Association, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Virginia State Bar, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Tobacco Indemnification & Community Revitalization Commission, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Tourism Corporation, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Trails, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Western Community College, 2004 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Wine Industry, 2001-2002 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Virginians For Justice, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Waste Management
      - 1998-2002 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      - 2003 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Wildlife Foundation of Virginia, undated (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - William & Mary Political Action Committee, 2002 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Winery Issues, 2002-2005 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Wine Study Work Group, 2001-2002 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Wise County Data Center, 2005 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Women's Issues, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Workforce Development, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Workforce Training, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Oversized, 2001-2004., Extent: 1 box. (Box 101)